Guide to the Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives Collection of Labor Movement Serials WAG.345
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series I: Labor unions and organizations, 1891-2012; 188.25 Linear Feet in 24 record cartons and 139 oversize flat boxes
  - Subseries I.L: Transportation Workers, 1938-2012; 23 Linear Feet in 2 record cartons and 18 oversize flat boxes
    - Speaking Out: Communications Workers of America, Local 3601, Detroit, MI, 1986 (Box 123, Folder 102)
    - C.A.M.: Concerned Autoworkers Movement, Fremont, CA, 1979 (Box 73, Folder 52)
    - Rank and File Advocate: Concerned Members of New Directions/TWU 100, Bronx, NY, 2001-2005 (Box 117, Folder 6)
    - From the Horse's Mouth: Concerned Rank and File Teamsters (CRAFT), Pittsburgh, Pa, 1975, 1979-1981 (Box 117, Folder 7)
    - Grapevine: Concerned Truckers for a Democratic Union, Chicago, IL, 1975-1976 (Box 117, Folder 8)
    - Taxi Union News: Democratic Union Organizing Committee Local 777, Chicago, IL, 1966-1968 (Box 118, Folder 1)
    - 1250 News: Department Store Employees Union, New York, NY, 1938-1939 (Box 40, Folder 10)
    - Unity News: Department Store Workers Committee For Unity, New York, NY, 1953 (Box 73, Folder 53)
    - Teamsters Rank and File Speaks: Detroit Metro TDU, Detroit, MI, 1982 (Box 118, Folder 2)
    - RPM: Detroit Organizing Committee, Detroit, MI, 1970-1972 (Box 118, Folder 3-4)
    - Federated Railwayman: Division No. 4, Railway Employees' Department, Montreal, Canada, 1953 (Box 73, Folder 54)
    - Durham Express: Durham Unity Team, Washington, DC, 1991 (Box 73, Folder 55)
    - Rank & File Reformer: Eastern PA. T.D.U., Analomink, PA, 1979 (Box 73, Folder 56)
    - UAW Ammunition: Education Department, International Union, United Automobile, Aircraft and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, Detroit, MI, 1971 (Box 73, Folder 57)
    - 719 News: Electro-Motive Diesel Workers Union - Local 719 UAW, Brookfield, IL, 1948 (Box 73, Folder 58)
    - Voice of Local 259: Executive Board of Local 259, 1947, 1949, 1954 (Box 118, Folder 5)
    - Federation News: Federation of Public Employees/Transport Workers Union, AFL-CIO, San Francisco, CA, 1970, 1972 (Box 118, Folder 6)
    - Ford World: Ford Motor Company, Employee Communication Department, Dearborn, MI, 1980 (Box 118, Folder 7)
    - Transport: Fraternite Canadienne des Employes de Chemins de fer et Autres Transports, Montreal, Canada, 1952 (Box 73, Folder 59)
    - Taxi News Transport: Fred Swartz, New York, NY, 1963-1966 (Box 118, Folder 8)
    - Teamster Pride: General Drivers, Chauffeurs and Helpers of Local 886, Oklahoma City, OK, 1991 (Box 73, Folder 60)
    - Union Dues: Graduate Employee Organization, 1992 (Box 118, Folder 9)
    - Hawaiian Teamster Organizer: Hawaii Teamsters & Allied Workers Union, 1977 (Box 118, Folder 11)
    - Local 707 News: Highway and Local Motor Freight Drivers, Dockmen and Helpers Local Union No. 707, Woodside, NY, 1980 (Box 73, Folder 61)
    - Workers' Unity: Hydramatic Chapter of Autoworkers United to Fight in '76, 1977 (Box 73, Folder 62)
    - IDA News: Independent Drivers Association, Denver, CO, 1975 (Box 173, Folder 2)
    - Skilled Tradesman: Independent Skilled Trades Council (UAW), Detroit, MI, 1975, 1978-1980, undated (Box 118, Folder 12)
    - ITOC News: Independent Taxi Owners Council, Inc./Hosynd Publications, Inc., Glen Cove, NY, 1976, 1984 (Box 118, Folder 13)
    - Interborough Bulletin: Interborough Rapid Transit Company, New York, NY, 1935, 1937-1938 (Box 118, Folder 14)
    - 840 News: International Brotherhood of Teamsters, New York, NY, 1980-1984 (Box 118, Folder 15)
    - IBT News: International Brotherhood of Teamsters, New York, NY, 1947 (Box 118, Folder 16)
    - News from the New Teamsters: International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Washington, DC, 1996 (Box 73, Folder 63)
    - Teamster Leader: International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Washington, DC, 1993, 1996 (Box 73, Folder 64)
    - Teamster News: International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Washington, DC, 1982 (Box 73, Folder 65)
    - Teamster Organizer: International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Washington, DC, 1995 (Box 73, Folder 66)
    - Teamster UPS Update: International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Washington, DC, 1995 (Box 73, Folder 67)
    - Teamsters Freight Bulletin: International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Washington, DC, 1994-1995 (Box 73, Folder 68)
    - Teamsters On Parade "79" News: International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Tampa, FL, 1992 (Box 123, Folder 103)
    - Teamsters 102 News: International Brotherhood of Teamsters - Local 102, Newark, NJ, 1964-1968 (Box 119, Folder 1)
    - Local 237 Member to Member: International Brotherhood of Teamsters - Local 237, Staten Island, NY, 1994 (Box 119, Folder 2)
    - 237 Teamster News and Views: International Brotherhood of Teamsters - Local 237, City Employees Union, New York, NY, 1986 (Box 73, Folder 69)
    - Voice of Teamsters: International Brotherhood of Teamsters - Local 391, Greensboro, NC, 1993 (Box 73, Folder 70)
    - 560 Teamster Journal: International Brotherhood of Teamsters - Local 560, Union City, NJ, 1991 (Box 119, Folder 3)
    - Reel News: International Brotherhood of Teamsters - Local 817, Lake Success, NY, 1992 (Box 172, Folder 44)
    - 840 News: International Brotherhood of Teamsters - Local 840, New York, NY, 1988, 1990 (Box 73, Folder 64)
    - Local 89 Teamster: International Brotherhood of Teamsters - Local 89, Louisville, KY, 1992 (Box 73, Folder 71)
    - Team/Work: International Brotherhood of Teamsters - New School chapter of I.B.T. Local 1518, 1980 (Box 73, Folder 72)
    - St. Louis Teamsters' Research Bulletin: International Brotherhood of Teamsters - Research Department, Joint Council of Teamsters No. 13, St. Louis, MO, 1956 (Box 73, Folder 73)
    - Washington Log Book: International Organization of Masters, mates and Pilots, Washington, DC, 1957, 1959-1960 (Box 73, Folder 74)
    - Local 88 Bulletin: International Organization of Masters, Mates and Pilots - Local 88, New York, NY, 1962, 1970 (Box 119, Folder 4)
    - ITF Seafarers' Bulletin: International Transport Workers' Federation, 1989, 1997 (Box 73, Folder 75)
    - UAW Outlaws Discrimination: International Union of United Automobile, Aircraft, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America (UAW), 1946 (Box 123, Folder 104)
    - Southern California Teamster: Joint Council of Teamsters, No. 42, Los Angeles, CA, 1990 (Box 119, Folder 5)
    - Labor: Labor, Washington, DC, 1935, 1945-1946, 1969-1972, 1984, 1989 (Box 119, Folder 5-11, Box 120, Folder 1-8)
    - Railroad Notes: Labor Research Association, 1978 (Box 123, Folder 100)
    - In The Driver's Seat: Lease Drivers Coalition, New York, NY, circa 1993 (Box 73, Folder 76)
    - Union News: Local 1428, Pomona, CA, 1976-1981, 1988 (Box 73, Folder 77, Box 120, Folder 10-11)
    - Voice of 212: Local 212, Detroit, MI, 1960 (Box 73, Folder 78)
    - 237 Rank & File Action: Local 237 Rank & File Action Committee, Brooklyn, NY, circa 1990s (Box 73, Folder 79)
    - News: Local 338 RWDSU/UFCW, Rego Park, NY, 2003 (Box 73, Folder 80)
    - Headlight: Local 6, 1979 (Box 73, Folder 81)
    - By the Bulbs: Local 810 Members, circa 1980s (Box 73, Folder 82)
    - 810 Reformer: Local 810 Teamsters for Democracy, New York, NY, 1992, 1994-1995 (Box 73, Folder 83)
    - Taxi Teamster: Local 826 IBT-AFL, New York, NY, 1953-1960 (Box 120, Folder 9)
    - LUPA Newsline: Local Union Press Association, 1988-1989 (Box 73, Folder 84)
    - Changeover: Motor City Labor League, Detroit, MI, 1971-1972 (Box 121, Folder 1)
    - New York Taxi & Limousine Journal: N. Momenpour, Riverdale, NY, 1984 (Box 73, Folder 85)
    - CAW National Union Magazine: National Automobile, Aerospace and Agricultural Implement Workers Union of Canada (CAW-Canada), Willowdale, Canada, 1988 (Box 73, Folder 86)
    - Traction Labor: National Progressive Traction Workers League, Chicago, IL, 1938 (Box 73, Folder 87)
    - Rank and File Advocate: New Directions/TWU 100, Bronx, NY, 2002-2005 (Box 121, Folder 2)
    - Women in Construction: New Jersey Department of Transportation, Metuchen, NJ, 1989 (Box 73, Folder 88)
    - Teamster News: New Jersey Teamsters Council No. 78, International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Jersey City, NJ, 1977, 1990 (Box 121, Folder 3)
    - Working Teamster: New Jersey-New York Teamsters for a Democratic Union, New York, NY, 1992-1993 (Box 121, Folder 4)
    - On the Line: New York City Transit Police Department, New York, NY, 1971-1973 (Box 121, Folder 5)
    - Taxi Times: New York Taxi Drivers Alliance, Brooklyn, NY, 1964 (Box 121, Folder 6)
    - Shift-change: The Newspaper of the New York Taxi Workers Alliance: New York Taxi Workers Alliance, New York, NY, 2011-2012 (Box 121, Folder 7)
    - Workers Battle Automation: News & Letters, Detroit, MI, 1960 (Box 73, Folder 90)
    - Northwest Passage: Northwest Passage, Inc., Seattle, WA, 1979-1983 (Box 121, Folder 8-11)
    - On the Line: NY-NJ United Workers Organization Auto Committee, 1977 (Box 73, Folder 91)
    - Service Station Organizer: Organizer, San Pedro, CA, circa 1970s (Box 172, Folder 41)
    - PROD Dispatch: PROD, Inc., Washington, DC, 1977-1978, undated (Box 122, Folder 1-4)
    - Sparks: the paper of the Public Transport Workers Association: Public Transport Workers Association, North Richmond, Australia, 1994-2005, 2008, 2010 (Box 73, Folder 95-7)
    - Truth About TWU: Rank and file committee for a Democratic TWU, 1948 (Box 73, Folder 92)
    - Real Wheels: Rank and File Movement in Local 100, Bronx, NY, 1997 (Box 73, Folder 93)
    - Labor Round-Up: Retail, Wholesale & Department Store Union, AFL-CIO, Birmingham, AL, 1951-1952 (Box 121, Folder 12)
    - RWDSU Record: Retail, Wholesale & Department Store Union, AFL-CIO, New York, NY, 1963, 1982, 1986, 1988-1999, undated (Box 124, Folder 1-6)
    - Chicago Area Revolutionary Autoworker: Revolutionary Autoworkers Committee (UAW caucus), Chicago, IL, 1976 (Box 73, Folder 94)
    - Skilled Trades Coalition Election Bulletin: Skilled Trades Coalition - Local 595 UAW, 1978 (Box 123, Folder 2)
    - Skilled Trades Coalition News Letter: Skilled Trades Coalition - Local 595 UAW, 1978, undated (Box 123, Folder 1)
    - Steering Wheel: Steering Wheel Corp, Aurora, OH, 1973 (Box 122, Folder 5)
    - Crisis Bulletin: Straphangers United, New York, NY, circa 1980 (Box 123, Folder 3)
    - Relight: Sylvania Teamsters, Peabody, MA, 1980, undated (Box 123, Folder 4)
    - Their Medallion ~ Our Jobs!: A History and Perspective of the NY Taxi Industry: Taxi Rank & File Coalition, New York, NY, circa 1975 (Box 123, Folder 5)
    - Taxi Weekly: Taxi Weekly, Inc., New York, NY, 1964 (Box 122, Folder 6)
    - Local Vocal: Teamster Local 639, Washington, DC, 1993 (Box 123, Folder 6)
    - Teamster Convoy Dispatch: Teamster Rank and File, Detroit, MI, 1992, 1995, undated (Box 122, Folder 7)
    - Seattle Semi: Teamster Rank and File Monthly, Seattle, WA, circa 1970s (Box 127, Folder 4)
    - Fighting Teamster: Teamster Workers for a Fighting Union - Local 688, St. Louis, MO, 1982 (Box 123, Folder 7)
    - Defend Your Union: Teamster-Longshore Clubs, Communist Party, New York, NY, circa 1970s (Box 122, Folder 8)
    - 707 Teamster: Teamsters - Local 707, Hempstead, NY, 1992 (Box 123, Folder 8)
    - Teamsters Canada: Teamsters Canada, Laval, Canada, 1996 (Box 123, Folder 9)
    - Convoy Contract Bulletin: Teamsters for a Decent Contract, Cleveland, OH, 1976 (Box 123, Folder 10)
    - Convoy Clips - Articles from Convoy Dispatch: Teamsters for a Democratic Union, Detroit, MI, 1991 (Box 123, Folder 11)
    - Convoy Dispatch: Voice of Teamsters for a Democratic Union: Teamsters for a Democratic Union, Detroit, MI, 1979-1997 (Box 125, Folder 1-9, Box 126, Folder 1-10)
    - Getting it on with Teamsters For Teamsters: Teamsters for a Democratic Union, Flushing, NY, 1981 (Box 123, Folder 12)
    - NY/NJ Teamster Rank and File News: Teamsters for a Democratic Union, New York, NY, 1985-1988 (Box 122, Folder 9)
    - On the Move: Teamsters for a Democratic Union, Detroit, MI, 1997 (Box 173, Folder 1)
    - Rank & File Speaks: Teamsters for a Democratic Union, Wayne, MI, 1979 (Box 123, Folder 13)
    - Right to Vote Newsletter: Teamsters for a Democratic Union, Detroit, MI, circa 1980 (Box 123, Folder 14)
    - TDU Members Bulletin: Teamsters for a Democratic Union, Detroit, MI, 1984, undated (Box 123, Folder 15)
    - TDU Membership Newsletter: Teamsters for a Democratic Union, Detroit, MI, 1988 (Box 123, Folder 16)
    - TDU: 10 Years and Going Strong: Teamsters for a Democratic Union, circa 1975 (Box 123, Folder 17)
    - Teamsters for Teamsters: Teamsters for a Democratic Union, Flushing, NY, 1981 (Box 127, Folder 1)
    - NY-NJ Teamster Rank & File News: Teamsters for a Democratic Union - Area TDU Members, Bronx, NY, 1986 (Box 123, Folder 18)
    - Working Teamster: Teamsters for a Democratic Union - B.C.-Yukon Chapter, South Burnaby, Canada, 1978-1979 (Box 123, Folder 19)
    - Speak Out: Teamsters for a Democratic Union - Cleveland Area TDU, Cleveland, OH, 1981, 1983 (Box 127, Folder 2)
    - Minnesota Teamster Voice: Teamsters for a Democratic Union - Minnesota Teamsters for a Democratic Union, St. Paul, MN, 1993 (Box 123, Folder 20)
    - N.Y. T.D.U. Regional Newsletter: Teamsters for a Democratic Union - N.Y. T.D.U., Flushing, NY, 1983 (Box 123, Folder 21)
    - New York-New Jersey TDU News: Teamsters for a Democratic Union - New Jersey-New York Teamsters for a Democratic Union, Flushing, NY, 1980 (Box 123, Folder 22)
    - Working Teamster: Teamsters for a Democratic Union - New Jersey-New York Teamsters for a Democratic Union, New York, NY, 1992-1993, 1995 (Box 127, Folder 3)
    - Noticiero/News: Teamsters for a Democratic Union - TDU Local 912, 1980 (Box 123, Folder 23)
    - TDU Rank & File: Teamsters for a Democratic Union Local 237, 1978-1980 (Box 123, Folder 24)
    - Teamster Election News: Teamsters For An Informed Membership, circa 1980s (Box 123, Folder 25)
    - Missouri Teamster: Teamsters Joint Council 13, St Louis, Mo, 1969-1982, 1994 (Box 128, Folder 1-4, Box 129)
    - Connecticut Labor Gazette: Teamsters Joint Council 64 (Connecticut) Bricklayers, Laborers, and Ironworkers, CT, 1971-1973 (Box 127, Folder 5)
    - Spokesman: Teamsters Local Union 25, Boston, MA, 1994 (Box 123, Folder 26)
    - Teamsters' Pride 769: Teamsters Local Union 769, Miami, FL, 1989 (Box 123, Folder 27)
    - Contract Update: Teamsters UPS, Washington, DC, 1993 (Box 123, Folder 28)
    - Punching out: The Independent Slate/UAW, circa 1980s (Box 123, Folder 29)
    - UTOG News Caster: The United Taxi Owners Guild, US, 1964 (Box 127, Folder 6)
    - Taxi Truth: The United Yellow Taxi Guild, Inc., New York, NY, 1987 (Box 127, Folder 10)
    - Transit Crisis Coalition Newsletter: Transit Crisis Center, New York, NY, circa 1970s (Box 123, Folder 30)
    - Third Avenue Transit Victory: Transport Workers Union - Local 100, New York, NY, 1944 (Box 127, Folder 7)
    - CIO Transport Worker: Transport Workers Union - Local 156, Los Angeles, CA, 1941-1942 (Box 127, Folder 9)
    - T.W.U. Transport News: Transport Workers Union - Local 234, Philadelphia, PA, 1953, 1955, 1965-1967, 1973 (Box 127, Folder 11)
    - TWU Local 234 C.I.O. Transport News: Transport Workers Union - Local 234, Philadelphia, Pa, 1948-1972 (Box 127, Folder 12)
    - Flatbush Wheels: Transport Workers Union - Rank and File of TWU Local 100, Brooklyn, NY, 1990 (Box 123, Folder 31)
    - Utility Flame: Transport Workers Union (CIO) - Utility Division, Local 101, Brooklyn, NY, 1942-1943 (Box 127, Folder 13)
    - Utility News: Transport Workers Union (CIO) - Utility Division, Local 101, Brooklyn, NY, 1944, 1946 (Box 127, Folder 14)
    - N.O.P.S. Workers Transport Bulletin: Transport Workers Union of America, 1942 (Box 123, Folder 33)
    - Contact: Transport Workers Union of America - Air Transport Division - Local 500 (CIO), Miami, FL, 1945 (Box 123, Folder 34)
    - Local 552: Transport Workers Union of America - Air Transport Division - Local 552, New York, NY, 1977 (Box 123, Folder 35)
    - Transport/CIO Transport: Transport Workers Union of America - Local 156 (CIO), Los Angeles, CA, 1941 (Box 63, Folder 6)
    - Local 234 News: Transport Workers Union of America - Local 234 (CIO), Philadelphia, PA, 1975 (Box 123, Folder 36)
    - Local 250-A News: Transport Workers Union of America (AFL-CIO) - Local 250-A, San Francisco, CA, 1975 (Box 123, Folder 37)
    - Pacific Report: Transport Workers Union of America (AFL-CIO) - Local 505, San Bruno, CA, 1968, 1969, 1971 (Box 172, Folder 45)
    - Local 513 News: Transport Workers Union of America (AFL-CIO) - Local 513, Dallas, TX, 1972-1973 (Box 123, Folder 38)
    - Grievance Bulletin: Transport Workers Union of America (CIO) - Executive Board of Local 100, New York, NY, 1951 (Box 123, Folder 39)
    - Bulletin: Local 234 Philadelphia Edition: Transport Workers Union of America, CIO, New York, NY, 1946 (Box 129, Folder 5)
    - Wheels & Wings: Transportation Employees Association, Brooklyn, NY, 1967-1968 (Box 123, Folder 40)
    - T.U.C. News: Transportation Union of California, Los Angeles, CA, 1941 (Box 129, Folder 6)
    - 807 Teamster: Truck Drivers Union, Local 807 (IBT), New York, NY, 1954 (Box 123, Folder 41)
    - Skill: UAW International, Detroit, MI, 1993 (Box 123, Folder 42)
    - Eastern UAW Solidarity: United Auto Workers (UAW) (CIO), Detroit, MI, 1962 (Box 123, Folder 43)
    - Election Facts: United Auto Workers (UAW) (CIO), 1952 (Box 123, Folder 44)
    - Employee Retirement Income Security Act of 1974: United Auto Workers (UAW) (CIO) (Box 123, Folder 45)
    - Local 2000 Vanguard: United Auto Workers (UAW) (CIO), Avon Lake, OH, 1993 (Box 123, Folder 46)
    - Local 95 Union News: United Auto Workers (UAW) (CIO), Janesville, WI, 1993 (Box 123, Folder 47)
    - Moving Ahead: United Auto Workers (UAW) (CIO), 1983 (Box 123, Folder 48)
    - News from UAW: United Auto Workers (UAW) (CIO), Detroit, MI, 1970, 1977, 1999 (Box 123, Folder 49)
    - Pump Line: United Auto Workers (UAW) (CIO), Minneapolis, MN, 1993 (Box 123, Folder 50)
    - Rank & File News: United Auto Workers (UAW) (CIO), 1980 (Box 123, Folder 51)
    - Resolutions Committee Report Number Three: A Program for Canada: United Auto Workers (UAW) (CIO), Los Angeles, CA, 1977 (Box 123, Folder 52)
    - Solidarity is the Banner: United Auto Workers (UAW) (CIO), 1966 (Box 123, Folder 53)
    - The Real Issues: United Auto Workers (UAW) (CIO), Detroit, MI, 1984 (Box 123, Folder 54)
    - The Voice of New Directions: United Auto Workers (UAW) (CIO), St. Louis, MO, 1990, 1994 (Box 123, Folder 55)
    - UAW-AFL GM Worker: United Auto Workers (UAW) (CIO), Detroit, MI, 1940 (Box 123, Folder 56)
    - UAW-CIO Ammunition: United Auto Workers (UAW) (CIO), Indianapolis, IN, 1950 (Box 123, Folder 57)
    - Voice of Labor: United Auto Workers (UAW) (CIO), Rochester, NY, 1993 (Box 123, Folder 58)
    - 400 Watchword: Official Publication, UAW Amalgamated Local 400: United Auto Workers (UAW) (CIO) - Amalgamated Local 400, Detroit, MI, 1984 (Box 129, Folder 7)
    - Watchword: United Auto Workers (UAW) (CIO) - Amalgamated Local 400, Detroit, MI, 1984 (Box 173, Folder 4)
    - Exhaust: United Auto Workers (UAW) (CIO) - International Harvester Co. - Local 98, Indianapolis, IN, 1956, 1961 (Box 123, Folder 59)
    - Ford Facts: United Auto Workers (UAW) (CIO) - Local 200, Windsor, Ontario, 1954 (Box 123, Folder 60)
    - Local 259 News: United Auto Workers (UAW) (CIO) - Local 259, New York, NY, 1959-1961, 1966 (Box 123, Folder 61)
    - Unity News Local 259: United Auto Workers (UAW) (CIO) - Local 259, New York, NY, 1973-1975, 1980, 1983-1987 (Box 129, Folder 10, Box 131, Folder 3)
    - Aero-Notes / Local 365: United Auto Workers (UAW) (CIO) - Local 365, Newark, NJ, 1943 (Box 129, Folder 9)
    - Union Forum: United Auto Workers (UAW) (CIO) - Local 549, Mansfield, OH, 1993 (Box 173, Folder 3)
    - Rank & File Newsletter: United Auto Workers (UAW) (CIO) - Local 551, 1980 (Box 123, Folder 62)
    - Assembler: United Auto Workers (UAW) (CIO) - Local 595, Linden, NJ, 1981 (Box 129, Folder 8)
    - Assembler: United Auto Workers (UAW) (CIO) - Local 595, Lincoln, NJ, 1982, undated (Box 123, Folder 64)
    - Local 595 Shop News Bulletin: United Auto Workers (UAW) (CIO) - Local 595, 1979 (Box 123, Folder 63)
    - Eye Opener: United Auto Workers (UAW) (CIO) - Local 598, Flint, MI, 1981 (Box 123, Folder 65)
    - Bulletin: United Auto Workers (UAW) (CIO) - Local 6, Melrose Park, IL, 1948 (Box 123, Folder 66)
    - Hi-Flyer: United Auto Workers (UAW) (CIO) - Local 6, Melrose Park, IL, 1948 (Box 123, Folder 67)
    - Searchlight: United Auto Workers (UAW) (CIO) - Local 659, Flint, MI, 1990 (Box 123, Folder 68)
    - Delco Sparks: United Auto Workers (UAW) (CIO) - Local 662, Anderson, IN, 1993 (Box 123, Folder 69)
    - Lampmaker: United Auto Workers (UAW) (CIO) - Local 663, 1954 (Box 123, Folder 70)
    - Dive Bomber: United Auto Workers (UAW) (CIO) - Local 856, Akron, OH, 1944 (Box 123, Folder 71)
    - The Local 879 UAW Autoworker: United Auto Workers (UAW) (CIO) - Local 879, St. Paul, MN, 1990 (Box 123, Folder 72)
    - Militant Auto Worker: United Auto Workers (UAW) (CIO) - Militant Solidarity Caucus of UAW Local 906, Fort Lee, NJ, 1974 (Box 123, Folder 73)
    - Research Bulletin: United Auto Workers (UAW) (CIO) - Research Department, Detroit, MI, 1941, 1984 (Box 123, Folder 74)
    - How the UAW-CIO Operates: United Auto Workers of America (UAW) (CIO), 1949 (Box 123, Folder 75)
    - Airline Facts: United Auto Workers of America (UAW) (CIO) - Airline Workers Department, Miami, FL, 1948 (Box 123, Folder 76)
    - Bishop Shiel on McCarthy: United Auto Workers of America (UAW) (CIO) - Education Conference, Detroit, MI, 1954 (Box 123, Folder 77)
    - How to Conduct a Union Meeting: United Auto Workers of America (UAW) (CIO) - Education Department, Detroit, MI, circa 1940s (Box 123, Folder 78)
    - Inside City Hall: United Auto Workers of America (UAW) (CIO) - Education Department, Detroit, MI, circa 1950s (Box 123, Folder 79)
    - Sharing Our Pride: United Auto Workers of America (UAW) (CIO) - Ford National Education, Development and Training Center, Dearborn, MI, 1992 (Box 123, Folder 80)
    - UAW-GM Report: United Auto Workers of America (UAW) (CIO) - GM Canada, Canada, 1984 (Box 123, Folder 82)
    - Auto-Aircraft News: United Auto Workers of America (UAW) (CIO) - Local 1037/UAW News Agency, Los Angeles, CA, 1951 (Box 123, Folder 81)
    - Progressive Movement Newsletter: United Auto Workers of America (UAW) (CIO) - Local 1183, 1979 (Box 123, Folder 83)
    - Local 879 UAW Autoworker: United Auto Workers of America (UAW) (CIO) - Local 879, St. Paul, MN, 1993 (Box 123, Folder 84)
    - New Contract: United Auto Workers of America (UAW) (CIO) - Local 980, 1981 (Box 123, Folder 86)
    - We've Got Rights: Know Them and Use Them: United Auto Workers of America (UAW) (CIO) - Local 980, circa 1980 (Box 123, Folder 87)
    - Delegates Report to the Members of Local #980: United Auto Workers of America (UAW) (CIO) - Local 980, circa 1970s (Box 172, Folder 43)
    - UAW Local 980 leaflets: United Auto Workers of America (UAW) (CIO) - Local 980, 1980 (Box 123, Folder 85)
    - Kick the Company Out of the Union!: United Auto Workers of America (UAW) (CIO) - Rank & File, circa 1980s (Box 123, Folder 88)
    - Region 9 News Bulletin: United Auto Workers of America (UAW) (CIO) - Region 9, Cranford, NJ, 1981 (Box 123, Folder 89)
    - Local 259 News: United Automobile Workers of America, New York, NY, 1964-1966 (Box 131, Folder 1)
    - Auto Workers Voice: United Automobile, Aircraft and Agricultural Implement Workers of America (UAW) - Local 259, 1945 (Box 123, Folder 90)